deconf.com 2019-02-23

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy for deconf.com

If you need more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, feel free to contact us by email or using our contact form.

At deconf.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by deconf.com and how it is used.

### Log Files and Web Analytics

Like many other Web sites, deconf.com makes use of log files and web analytics services. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages and number of clicks. We use these stats to analyze trends, administer the site and track user’s movements around the site. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

As third-party  technologies, we use Google Analytics and DoubleClick Cookies, to collect non-personal information, when you use our online site, in the form of various usage and user metrics. These tools and technologies collect and analyze certain types of information, including demographic and interests data, cookies, IP addresses, device and software identifiers, referring and exit URLs, on-site behavior and usage information, feature use metrics and statistics, and other similar information.

You may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the [Google Analytics opt-out page](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). For more information also check Google’s [Remarketing Privacy Guidelines](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=100746) and [Restrictions](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=178363).

### Cookies and Web Beacons

deconf.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences and user-specific actions, to customize a webpage based on visitor’s browser type or to store information that the visitor sends via their browser.

#### DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on deconf.com.

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit on deconf.com and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out for the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy [at the following URL](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

To learn more about Google products, how the information sent by your browsers is used and how you can control the information sent to Google, check out this resource [How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/).

#### Other Cookies

Some of our advertising partners may also use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our current advertising partners include: Google Adsense, Media.net, Clicky.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use their own technology to deliver advertisements through deconf.com to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

#### Final notes

deconf.com has no access to or control over these cookies. that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. deconf.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your personal browser options. For more detailed information about cookie management on your specific web browser, consult your browser’s official website.
